https://www.waschoolcanteens.org.au/privacy/

Registered Products
What’s new?
Projects
MenuMembershipStarCAP2Star Choice™ ProgramDatabase IntroductionRegistered ProductsWhat's new?Product DatabaseSchool CommunityParent bodyParentsPrincipalsTeachersCanteensCase studies – HarvesteCanteensFinancial managementFood allergyFood safety and hygieneMenu developmentResourcesRobin Bromley Visionary GrantsVolunteersTrainingTraining scheduleWASCA trainingOther trainingOnline Traffic Light TrainingTAFERecipesDips and spreadsSaladsSavourySoupsSweetFAQsNewsProjects
Privacy
A-
A+
Home » Privacy
The Western Australian School Canteen Association Inc. (WASCA) does not attempt to collect Personal Information* about you when you visit this website. You can generally visit this website without revealing Personal Information*, unless you choose to provide it. The information collected by The Western Australian School Canteen Association Inc. (WASCA) is dependant upon the actions undertaken when visiting the website.
Site Visit Data
The Western Australian School Canteen Association Inc. (WASCA) records each visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes:
the user’s server address
the type of browser used to access the site
the date and time the user accessed the site
the pages accessed
This information assists The Western Australian School Canteen Association Inc. (WASCA) to understand how the website is used and helps to keep improving information quality.
The Western Australian School Canteen Association Inc. (WASCA) will make no attempt to identify users or their browsing activities, except where required by law.
This website may contain links to other sites. The Western Australian School Canteen Association Inc. (WASCA) is not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other websites and encourages you to examine each site’s privacy policy and make your own decisions regarding it’s accuracy, reliability and the correctness of material and information found.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of information delivered to and stored by your web browser when you access information from certain websites. The Western Australian School Canteen Association Inc. (WASCA) may use cookies from time to time as an effort to improve user experience.
Email Management – Collection of Personal Information
Your email address will only be recorded if you choose to send a message. It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list, unless explicitly stated. Your email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.
If you are asked for any other Personal Information* you will be informed how it will be used if you choose to give it.
* The use of the term “Personal Information” in this privacy statement means any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.
Western Australian School Canteen Association (Inc.)
PO Box 3484, East Perth WA 6892 | Telephone: 08 9264 4999 | Email: wasca@education.wa.edu.au
Copyright 2020
WASCA.
Privacy | Disclaimer | Copyright |
Website Design by Lethal Graphics
